{
    "subject": "Robert_Stevenson__director_",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Anna_Lee",
    "human_readable": "Robert Stevenson, the director, is married to Anna Lee.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9377702474594116,
            "question": "Are Robert Stevenson and Anna Lee a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8907985687255859,
            "question": "Is Anna Lee married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8536994457244873,
            "question": "Who is Robert Stevenson married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.650127649307251,
            "question": "Who is Anna Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6500808596611023,
            "question": "What is the name of Robert Stevenson's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49983590841293335,
            "question": "Is Robert Stevenson an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42005661129951477,
            "question": "What is Robert Stevenson's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3882778584957123,
            "question": "Does Anna Lee have any other notable relationships?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29362377524375916,
            "question": "Has Robert Stevenson worked on any famous films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2612308859825134,
            "question": "What does Robert Stevenson do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Stevenson, the director, is married to Anna Lee.",
            "html": "yago_29822_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Robert Stevenson worked on any famous films?",
            "html": "yago_29822_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Anna Lee have any other notable relationships?",
            "html": "yago_29822_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Robert Stevenson's profession?",
            "html": "yago_29822_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29822_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Robert Stevenson, the director, is married to Anna Lee. The documents mention that Robert Stevenson was previously married to Anna Lee (1934 - 1944) and Frances Howard. This directly implies that he was indeed married to Anna Lee."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Robert Stevenson, the director, is married to Anna Lee.\" The details in multiple files confirm their marriage from 1934 to 1944."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state Robert Stevenson divorced Anna Lee in March of 1944.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}